怎么了
What is it?
不是  我不知道想吃什么
Nothing.I can't find anything to eat.
我吃什么都会恶心
Everything makes me nauseous.
告诉你们  怀孕真不是件容易的事[蛋糕]
I'm telling you, being pregnant is no piece of cake
啊  蛋糕
Oh, cake!
亲爱的  抱歉
Honey, I'm sorry.
什么味道  是浴室里传出来的
What is that smell?It's coming from the bathroom.
怀孕倒是让你多了不少怪癖
Pregnancy does give you some weird cravings.
是我  菲比  这里有我想吃的东西
It’s me. It’s Phoebe. Listen there's something in here I want to eat.
什么味道这么香
What smells so good?
是洗发水吗  番石榴香味的
Is it the shampoo? It's guava.
不是
No.
等一下
Wait. Wait.
是我的红肠三明治吗
Is it my bologna sandwich?
是  是  是
Yes. Yes. Yes.
真不敢相信
I can't believe it!
宝宝想吃红肠  我却不能吃肉
The baby wants bologna! Maybe he wants me to eat meat? I can't eat meat!
等一下
Wait!
也许是酸黄瓜
Maybe it's the pickle!
你在写什么
What are you writing?
约书亚明天回来
Joshua's coming in tomorrow,
既然我没胆量约他
and since I don't have the guts to ask him out. . .
那我就卖他一件外套
. . .I'm gonna sell him a coat
再把这纸条塞进衣服口袋
and put this note in the pocket.
约书亚  有空打电话给我
'Joshua, give me a call sometime.
象你这样的人
Guys like you...
...永不过时
...never go out of style. '
你扔掉的纸上都写了什么
What did you throw away?
-大伙都在啊  -你们干什么去了
- Hi, guys. - What have you been up to?
我们去参观了维多利亚时期门把手展
We went to see a collection ofvictorian doorknobs at the museum.
居然不带我去
Without me?
是我叔叔硬拖我们去的
My uncle dragged us there,
不过其实展览还挺有意思的
But, it actually it turned out to be really interesting.
那些门把很华丽  不信你们看
They were so ornate and beautiful. Look at that.
我不知道英国博物馆是怎么个规矩
I don't know how museums work in England,
但在我们这里  顺手牵羊是不对的
but here, you're not supposed to take stuff.
这是从礼品店搞来的
I got it from the gift shop.
那里的安保太松懈了
They have really lax security.
开玩笑的
It's a joke.
-我得走了  再会  -再会
- I've got to be off. See you. Bye bye then. - Bye bye then.
看来你们处得不错
You're having a good time.
她很不错  也很有意思
She is amazing, and she's so much fun.
而且你们知道吗
And you know what?
和她在一起  我也很快乐
When I'm with her, I'm fun!
我甚至还报了直升机驾驶课
I even signed up for helicopter classes.
她过两天就走了  我不必真学
She's leaving in two days. I don't have to do it.
两天  你一定很失望吧
In two days? You must be bummed.
她非回去不可  不过我开始就有心理准备
She's got to go back, but I've been prepared for this from the start.
我们都知道只有两周能在一起  仅此而已
We knew we had two weeks together and then that's it.
我的每段恋情都这样
That's what all my relationships are like.
但在罗斯的恋情中
But in Ross' case,
"双方"都知道只有二个星期
they both know two weeks, that's it.
-菲比 -嘿  嘿
- Pheebs! - Hello. Hello.
我知道  我知道  好啦
Yeah, I know. I know!
宝宝想吃肉想疯了
The baby is totally craving meat.
我下午想用素肉堡骗他
This afternoon, I made it a soy burger,
让他以为自己吃到了肉
so that it'd think it was getting meat.
结果我就反胃了
And I got nauseous.
也许是因为素肉堡巨难吃无比
Maybe that's because soy burgers suck!
怀孕可把我的胃害惨了
Pregnancy is hard on your tummy.
但你身上有一种孕妇的光彩
But you got that cool pregnant-lady glow.
那是汗  你要是吐一早上  也会有这样光彩的
That's sweat. You throw up all morning, you’ll have that glow too.
-这是你要的风衣  -太棒了
- Here's that trench coat you wanted. - Great.
很舒服
It's comfortable.
这下我就可以出去当暴露狂了
You could really flash somebody in this.
不行  不行  出了店门
Don't put your hands in the pockets
才能把手放进口袋里
until you are out of the store.
为什么不行
Why not?
因为...
Well, because...
有很多人...
...we get a lot of--
他们真是害群之马
They ruin it for everybody.
没错
I know.
我昨晚穿着那件羊毛衫去约了个会
Y'know, I wore that cashmere sweater on a date last night.
我离婚后的第一次约会
It was the first date since the divorce.
恭喜  你爱她吗
Congratulations. So do you love her?
她还不错  不过这也让我发现
She's nice, but it made me realize...
我其实还没有心情约会
...I'm just not ready to be dating.
有点意思
That's interesting.
-那是什么  -防盗磁条
-What was that? -Just an anti-theft device.
那这是什么
And what's this?
这个和这个  你都需要的
You need that, you need that too
因为很明显  贼会把它给撕掉的
cause obviously, a thief could just tear this up.
今晚开派对
Listen, we-we have to have a party tonight!
事实上派对五分钟后就开始
Actually, we have to have one in five minutes,
有事的快取消
so everybody cancel your plans.
-什么情况  -怎么了
- What are you talking about? - What's going on?
我们要给艾蜜莉办"惊喜欢送会"
We have to have a surprise Bon Voyage party for Emily.
但其实是为了约书亚
But it's actually for Joshua.
他说  他还没有心情约会
He said he's not ready to date.
所以  我不得不邀请他参加派对
So I had to invite him to a party
这样我才能在工作之外见到他
if I wanted to see him outside of work.
现在我制造了一个色诱他的完美机会
And now I have created the perfect opportunity to seduce him.
虽然我很想当面警告约书亚
As much as I'd like to meet Josh and warn him. . .
但我和艾蜜莉不会参加派对
Emily and I won't be here.
她会先来和大家道别
She'll come by to say goodbye.
然后我已经安排了整晚的节日
I've got a special evening planned.
抱歉  没有派对了
Sorry. No party.
惊喜
Surprise!
从没有人给我办过惊喜派对
No one's thrown me a surprise party before.
其实  这都是罗斯的主意
Well, it was all Ross' idea.
你真好
You're so sweet.
我好惊喜
And I'm so surprised.
你真的没料到
You didn't know?
约书亚在那边  你怎么在这边
Why are you here if Joshua's all the way over there?
我想欲擒故纵
I'm trying to play hard-to-get.
快  他在看这边  快说句好笑的话
Oh, quick he's looking over here, say something funny.
比如
Like what?
什么事这么好笑
What's so funny?
我说"比如"
"Like what?"
真深奥
Now that's a thinker.
欲擒故纵不起作用
This playing-hard-to-get thing is not working.
把樱桃给我
Hand me those cherries.
-要吃樱桃吗  -不用了  谢谢
- Care for a cherry? - No, thanks.
我可以用舌头  给樱桃梗打个结
I can tie one of these into a knot using just my tongue.
你还好吗
You okay?
All right?
我们得赶快走了
We should probably get going soon.
但是派对才刚开始啊
But the party's just getting started.
我们得在15分钟内  赶去四季餐厅喝酒
We have to be at The Four Seasonsfor drinks in 15 minutes.
然后去广场饭店吃个晚饭
Then The Plaza for dinner.
那你为什么还办派对
Why did you plan a party at the same time?
其实美国的惊喜派对都很短
Actually, American surprise parties are very short.
通常都"惊喜"
It's usually, "Surprise! "
然后就"我好惊喜喔   再见"
Then, "My God, I'm so surprised. Bye! "
罗斯  但我在这玩得很开心
But I'm having such a great time.
你妹妹说  你曾经扮成老太太...
Your sister has just been telling me that you dressed up like old ladies. . .
举办了一场假的荼会
...and hosted make-believe tea parties.
莫妮卡说的  是吧
Monica said that, did she?
你接下来要放什么
Then what are you going to put on top of that?
一点蒜味腊肠
A little salami.
那蒜味腊肠上面呢
What goes on top of the salami?
放点熏牛肉
Pastrami.
你真是个天才
You're a genius.
帮我拉一下拉链
Give me a hand with the zipper.
是住上拉
Up!
-你换了衣服  -对  我需要我的幸运裙
-You changed? - I just needed my lucky dress.
-幸运是指露更多乳沟  -我觉得是
-Lucky means more cleavage? -It does for me.
你们看  他多帅啊
Look at him! He's so cute.
真想过去  一把抱住他  好好亲一口
I just want to grab him and kiss him.
但是他不知道我喜欢他
How could I kiss him without him knowing I like him?
我有个办法
I know how you can get him.
脱胸罩吧
Take off your bra.
-什么  -在《煽癫舞》里...
- What? - This scene in Footloose--
-是《闪电舞》[电影名]   -对对
- Flashdance. - Yeah.
-那个女水管工  -是焊工
- With that plumber girl? - She's a welder.
你是参演了还是怎么地啊
Were you, like, in the movie?
她在衣服底下脱掉胸罩
She takes off her bra under the shirt
再从袖子里抽出来
and pulls it out the sleeve.
非常性感  而且很有格调
very sexy. And classy.
-或者用槲寄生  -现在又不是圣诞节
-Or you could use mistletoe. -It's not Christmas.
-转瓶子  -他又不是小孩子
- Spin the bottle. - He's not 11 .
谢谢你们  你们真用心
Thank you so much for this. It was so thoughtful of you.
你们要走了
You're leaving?
-对  我们还有事  -我也要走了
-Yes, we have something we have to get to. -I'll take off too.
先别走  都留下
You guys can't leave yet. You have to stay.
我们准备了重头戏的
We've got the whole big thing planned.
什么重头戏
What big thing?
转瓶子的规则是  我转瓶子
Spin-The-Bottle works like this: I spin.
指向甘瑟  于是我就要亲甘瑟一下
Lands on Gunther, so I'd kiss Gunther.
谁要先来
Who wants to go first?
我先来
I'll go.
欢迎来到美国
Welcome to America.
天哪
Oh, my God!
二连击  来个舌吻吧
Two in a row! You gotta use your tongues now.
再来
All right.
太巧了
What are the odds?
够了
That's enough!
让别人玩吧
Let's let someone else play.
你不想玩  干嘛来派对啊
If you didn't want to play, then why'd you come to the party?
该我了
Okay, my turn!
看啊
Look at that!
我的上帝
Oh, my God.
宝宝踢我了
The baby just kicked!
没事的  没事的
It's okay. It's okay.
他还会接着踢的
If it kicked once, it'll kick again!
大家要记住刚才的位置
Everybody just remember where they were sitting.
有个虫
It's a bug.
不管我多想吃
It doesn't matter how much I'm craving it.
我都不吃肉  那是冷血谋杀
I'll never eat meat. It's cold-blooded murder.
我的三文治上长了个菲比
There's a Phoebe on my sandwich!
菲比  你干什么
Phoebe, what are you doing?
我没办法
I can't help it!
我要吃肉  宝宝要吃肉
I need the meat! The baby needs the meat.
要是与人拍拖  那你就得专一
You know when you dating someone, you don't want to cheat
除非第三者真的很火辣
unless it's with someone really hot.
那当然
Totally.
吃肉也一样
This is the same kind of deal.
既然错了
If you do something wrong...
就要错得漂亮
do it right.
好点没
Feel better?
好点了  但我付出的代价呢
Yeah, but at what cost?
三餐吃肉吃半年
Six months, three meals a day?
我会因此吃掉...几百万头牛
I am going to eat like, you know, millions of cows.
要是我帮你平衡过来呢
What if I said I can even things out for you, meat-wise?
-什么  -我很能吃肉对吧
- What? - I eat a lot of meat, right?
要是在宝宝出生前  我戒吃肉
But suppose, until the baby's born, I laid off it.
这样就不会多死动物了
No extra animals would die.
你只是在吃我那份
You'd just be eating my animals.
真不敢想信  你愿意为我这么做
I can't believe you'd do that for me.
当然愿意  我也可以吃素
Absolutely! I could be a vegetarian.
啤酒里没有肉吧
There's no meat in beer, right?
如果不吃开胃菜   马上买单
We can still make dinner if we skip the appetizers
兴许我们还赶得上吃主菜
and ask for our check right away.
我们现在不能走  瑞秋要表演了
We can't go now. Rachel is going to put on a skit.
天哪  你疯了吗
Oh, my God! Have you lost your mind?
不  我终于想通了
No no no, I am finally thinking clearly.
我的幸运裙效果不佳
My lucky dress wasn't working too well for me.
但四年来  这套衣服百发百中
But for four years, this baby never missed.
瑞秋  我不能让你
Wait, I can't let--
好吧  其实我也想看热闹
Actually, I want to see what happens.
好棒的行头
Nice costume.
是啊  我想给艾蜜莉来个美式的再见欢呼
Well, I wanted to give Emily a big American goodbye cheer.
预备  起
Ready. Ok.
给我一个E
Give me an "E" !
给我一个M
Give me an "M" !
给我一个I
Give me an "I" !
给我一个L
Give me an "L" !
给我一个Y
Give me a "Y" !
加起来是什么
What do you get?
艾蜜莉
EMILY!
以此欢送艾蜜莉
That's me as a cheerleader!
有颗牙松了
I loosened a tooth.
不过没事  我有牙医的
It's no big deal. I have a dentist.
我得冰敷下  失陪了
I'll put some ice on it. Excuse me.
怎么办  怎么办
What do I do now?
你完蛋了
I think you're done.
该脱胸罩了
Time to take off the bra.
刚才的表演很精彩
That was really great.
但是我得走了
But I got to take off.
脱...胸...罩
Take the bra off.
我陪你去拿外套
Let's go get your coat.
瑞秋是我女朋友
Rachel's my girlfriend.
今晚蛮开心的
So this was really fun.
是啊  很开心
Yeah, it was real fun.
这件胸罩...
You know, this bra...
实在很不舒服
is really bothering me.
这里以前是我的卧室
This used to be my bedroom.
有很多回忆  很多很多的回亿
A lot of memories in here. Lot of memories.
要是墙壁会说话  它们一定会说
If these walls could talk, they'd say:
想听听往事吗
"Want to hear some memories?"
要帮忙吗
Need a little hand there?
不用  没问题
I got this all under control.
可是看起来不像
You really don't seem like you do.
算了  真是的
God! Forget it!
事情不该是这样的
This is not how this was supposed to happen.
不然应该怎样
What was supposed to happen?
你能不能不要看我
Can you not look at me when I say this?
我原以为要是能把你叫来...
I thought that if I could get you here...
就能色诱你
I could seduce you.
我上班从不穿西装
I don't wear suits to work.
却跟你买了六套
And I bought six of them from you.
抱歉  我还以为你有需要
I'm sorry. I thought you needed them.
我的意思是我一直去找你
My point is, I kept coming back
是因为我想见你
because I wanted to see you.
为什么
Why?
因为我喜欢你
Because I like you.
你喜欢我
You like me?
是啊  你漂亮  聪明又成熟
I mean, you're beautiful and smart and sophisticated.
当然今晚我是没看到啦
A lot of this isn't based on tonight.
但是你喜欢我
But you like me?
这段日子以来  我们竟然一直互相喜欢
I can't believe this. All this time, I liked you and you liked me!
不要说"但是"
No "but. "
"但是"都没好事  停在"我们互相喜欢"就好
"But" is never good. Let's leave it at "I like you and you like me. "
-然而  -那是个好听的"但是"
- However. - No, that's a fancy "but. "
我刚结束我的婚姻
My marriage, like, just ended.
我还没心情跟别人交住
And I'm really not ready to get into anything yet.
但是...
But...
对不起  我需要一点时问
I'm sorry. I just need a little time.
你在这里  我还在找你呢
There you are. I was looking for you.
约书亚走了  你和艾蜜莉可以走了
Joshua's gone, so you and Emily are free to go.
无所谓了
It's okay.
她还在里面享受这场假派对
She's still in there enjoying her fake party.
现在要做什么也来不及了
It's too late to do any of the stuff I had planned.
罗斯  抱歉  我毁了你美好的夜晚
Ross. I'm sorry. I ruined your evening.
我出了个大丑
If it makes you feel any better,
这有没有让你高兴一点
I made a fool of myself.
有一点点
Helps a little.
能让悲惨的失败者坐下来吗
Is there room there for a pathetic loser?
坐吧
Have a seat.
对不起
I'm so sorry.
没关系
It's okay.
反正只是一段两周的恋情
It was just a two-week thing anyway.
我只是不想就这样结束
I just didn't want it to end this way.
或许是你不想结束
Or maybe you didn't want it to end?
什么意思
What do you mean?
你似乎真的很喜欢她
You seem to really like her.
没错
I really do.
但我能怎么办  我们说好
What am I going to do? We agreed
只在一起待两周的
it'd be a two-week thing.
不对彼此承诺什么
No commitment.
那个女孩整晚都跟你的朋友嚷嚷着
That girl just spent the entire evening talking to your friends. . .
说是要听你的故事
asking to hear stories about you. . .
还拿莫妮卡的相簿来看
Iooking through Monica's photo albums.
只想二周的话  鬼才会这么做呢
You don't do that if you're just in it for two weeks.
是吗
You think?
她还有14个小时才去机场
You've got 1 4 hours until she has to be at the airport.
而你却坐在走廊上
And you're sitting here in a hallway. . .
陪一个28岁嘴肿起来的啦啦队员
with a 28-year-old cheerleader with a fat lip.
你说得对
You're right.
谢谢
Thanks.
在看哪一本相册
What photo album was it?
就是你跟一堆白化小孩的那个
It was you and a bunch of albino kids.
天哪  那不是白化小孩
Oh, my God! Those weren't albino kids.
那是电脑夏令营
That was computer camp!
-你是个悲惨的失败者  对吧  -我是
- You're a pathetic loser, right? - Oh, yeah.
坐
Sit!
嗨
Hi.
天哪  约书亚
Oh, my God. Joshua.
我刚才说  我还没有准备好
All those things I said about not being ready--
-那些都不是真话  -不  都是真话
-They're not true? -No, they're all true.
但是...
But…
我喜欢这个"但是"
I love that "but" .
要不要进去喝杯咖啡
Do you want to go inside and get some coffee?
百发百中
Every time.
-你放了什么  -熏牛肉
- What do you got there? - Pastrami.
-你知道什么跟它最配  -腌牛肉
- You know what goes good with that? - Corned beef.
我本想说红肠  但腌牛肉更棒
I was going to say bologna. But that's better.
-要不要放点熏火鸡肉  -好
- How about that smoked turkey? - Ok.
哦  妈呀
Oh, mama!
-宝宝什么时候生  -半年后
- When is the baby due? - Six months.
自然死亡的牛  我可以吃吧
If a cow died of natural causes, I could have one of those, right?
我会先下手的
Not if I get there first.